RG 003, New London County, County Court Files
Connecticut State Library
76James Kirby Martin, Benedict Arnold, Revolutionary Hero: An American Warrior Reconsidered (1997), 27-31. NLCC Files, June 1756, Box 105, folder 3.
77Ibid, Feb. 1730, Box 31, folder 3, no. 99.
78The State Library has extensive holdings of church records. RG 000, Classified Archives, contains a large quantity of Congregational Church records and lesser quantities of records of Baptist, Episcopalian, and other Protestant denominations. In RG 001, Early General Records, more church records can be found in the Connecticut Archives, Ecclesiastical Affairs. RG 070, Church Records, contains materials from an additional eighty plus Baptist, Congregational, Episcopal, Lutheran, and Methodist churches.
79See Denise Schenk Grosskopf, "The Limits of Religious Dissent in Seventeenth-Century Connecticut: The Rogerne Heresy" (Ph.D. dissertation, University of Connecticut, 1999).
80The two best studies of Baptists and Separatists are, William G. McLoughlin, New England Dissent, 1630-1833; the Baptists and the Separation of Church and State, 2 vols. (Cambridge, Mass., Harvard University Press, 1971); C. C. Goen, Revivalism and Separatism in New England, 1740-1800: Strict Congregationalist and Separate Baptists in the Great Awakening (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1962).
81NLCC Files, Sep. 1698, Box 1, folder 7; NLCC Trials, Vol. 7, Sep. 1698.
82Ibid, Feb. 1786, Box 196, folder 6, no. 101.
83Ibid, Nov. 1704, Box 2, folder 16.
84Ibid, June 1708, Box 3, folder 4; Sep. 1708, Box 4, folder 10; June 1709, Box 4, folder 13.
85Charles J. Hoadly, ed., The Public Records of the Colony of Connecticut, Vol. 7 (Hartford: Press of Case, Lockwood & Brainard, 1878), 257.
86NLCC Files, June 1731, Box 33, folder 4, no. 167.
87Ibid, June 1752, Box 93, folder 18, no. 201.
88Ibid, Feb. 1844, Box 407, folder 15, no. 94; June 1845, Box 410, folder 10, no. 429.
89Ibid, Nov. 1748, Box 86, folder 3, no. 79. The first time that the word "Separatist" was used occurred in June 1740 in Dom Rex v. James Hillhouse, Joseph Bradford, Daniel Fitch, and Alexander Johnston, all of New London. Hillhouse had been the first minister for the North Society in New London, now Montville, but had been dismissed and replaced by David Jewett. Hillhouse, however, continued to preach and was indicted for holding a separate meeting. Ibid, June 1740, Box 63, folder 14, no. 650.
90Ibid, June 1742, Box 73, folder 9, no. 634; NLCC Trials, Vol. 20, Nov. 1742, no. 338.
91John Lord v. Elisha Marvin, Jr., Josiah Ely, and Gamaliel Brockway, Ibid, Feb. 1791, Box 221, folder 18, no. 112.
92Ibid, Dec. 1792, Box 227, folder 9.
93Ibid, Box 91, folder 15. This case was in the No Docket files, thus, no decision was made by the county court
94Ibid, Feb. 1789, Box 213, folder 13.
95Ibid, June 1785, Box 192, folder 12.
96Ibid, June 1753, Box 97, folder 8.
97Timothy Lester et al v. John Green, Jr., Ibid, Nov. 1783, Box 182, folder 3, no. 84.
98Additional subjects include bribery, buggery or sodomy, extortion, fornication, keeping false books, profane swearing, and selling strong drink without a license.
99Ibid, June 1757, Box 106, folder 19, no. 93.
100Ibid, Nov. 1770, Box 155, folder 7, no. 121. The case was withdrawn.
101Ibid, Nov. 1770, Box 155, folder 8.
102Ibid, June 1805, Box 267, folder 12. The case was never brought to trial.
103Ibid, John Smith v. Jedediah Smith, June 1811, Box 290, folder 4.
104Ibid, Feb. 1850, Box 420, folder 16, no. 443. The defendant was found not guilty and the plaintiff appealed to the Superior Court.
105Ibid, Nov. 1854, Box 433, folder 17, no. 365.
106Ibid, Feb. 1796, Box 234, folder 20. Neither party appeared at trial. The case was placed in the sexual category.
107Grand jurors were annually elected by the freemen at the annual town meeting. They were charged to "diligently enquire after, and make due presentment of all misdemeanors and breaches of law, whereof they have cognizance." Statute Laws of the State of Connecticut (1808), 371-73.
108State v. Walter Edwards, NLCC Files, Nov. 1847, Box 411, folder 3, no. 566.
109State v. Rebecca Morgan, Ibid, Feb. 1787, Box 201, folder 15, no. 146.
110See for example, Nancy Hathaway Steenburg, Children and the Criminal Law in Connecticut, 1638-1855 (New York and London: Routlege, 2005).
111NLCC Files, Nov. 1834; Box 377, folder 13, 314, 319; folder 13, no. 249-50; folder 15, no. 332; folder 16, no. 343; folder 18, no. 323; folder 18, no. 302; folder 18, no. 336.
112Ibid, Boxes 414-15 passim
113Ibid, Box 346, folder 17.
114It is often difficult to differentiate between those who maintained bawdry houses and prostitutes, therefore, the fifty-sic total is accurate, but the ratio between the two is a matter of interpretation.
115NLCC Files, June 1840, Box 398, folder 14, no. 209, 211, 234, 238.
116Ibid, Feb. 1848, Box 415, folder 13, no. 667-71, 675, 677. People of color were disproportionately represented in such prosecutions, but conviction rates were comparable with those against whites. Sansom received a six-month sentence, a $50 fine, and compelled to pay court costs. Two of the women received both jail sentences and fines and the other two just fines.
117Ibid, Feb. 1848, Box 15, folder 12, no. 655, 662.
118Ibid, Nov. 1842, Box 404, folder 6, no. 80. Convicted of the crime by the Superior Court, the State's Attorney did not prosecute.
119Ibid, July 1847, Box 414, folder 5, no. 849.
120Ibid, Apr. 1851, Box 424, folder 11, no. 428.
121State v. William Johnson et al, Ibid, June 1820, Box 334, folder 1; State v. John L. Maples, June 1820, Box 334, folder 1; State v. David Carrier, June 1838, Box 394, folders 7, no. 187, 198, 199.
122Governor and Company v. Samuel Burrows, Ibid, June 1783, Box 181, folder 9.
123Roland Mather Hooker, The Spanish Ship Case: A Troublesome Episode for Connecticut, 1752-1758 (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1934), Tercentenary pamphlet XXV.
124Hoadly, ed., The Public Records of the Colony of Connecticut Vol. 12, 127-33.
125Albert E. Van Dusen, Connecticut (New York: Random House, 1961), 126, 434; Oscar Zeichner, Connecticut's Years of Controversy, 1750-1776 (Chapel Hill, N.C.: University of North Carolina Press, 1949), 46-48, 81-82, 131-32.
126See Richard Buel, Jr., Dear Liberty: Connecticut's Mobilization for the Revolutionary War. (1980) for detailed information on the State's problems at the closing stages of the American Revolution. He does not, however, use court records in his research.
127Twenty-three represent State prosecutions.
128NLCC Files, Nov. 1781, Box 171, folders 3, 4, 5, 20; Box 172, folders 1, 6, 10.
129Ibid, Box 195, folder 15, no. 23.
130Prosper Wetmore, Sheriff v. Selectmen of Stonington, Ibid, Feb. 1788, Box 206, folder 18, no. 123.
131The War of 1812 cases appear in the following court sessions: Dec. 1813 (1), June 1815 (1), Dec. 1815 (2), Mar. 1816 (3), Mar. 1817 (1), Dec. 1817 (1), Dec. 1818 (1), and June 1820 (1).
132Thomas Wilcox and Jesse Wilcox v. Edward Chesebrough et al, NLCC Files, Dec. 1809, Box 284, folder 22; Ibid, June 1810, Box 286, folder 17. On the first occasions, the parties failed to appear and the second case was not prosecuted.
133Roger Coit v. Joseph Stanton, Ibid, Dec. 1813, Box 300, folder 6, no. 148; Rowland Lee v. James Stewart, Ibid, Dec. 1818, Box 326, folder 18, no. 261.
134Other cases involving African Americans can be found in twenty-three volumes of Trials covering the period between 1666 and 1774. They are particularly useful for the period of time before Files became plentiful in 1702 and, in addition, sometimes contain documentation not found in Files
135Barbara W. Brown and James M. Rose, joint authors, Black Roots in Southeastern Connecticut, 1650-1900 (Detroit: Gale Research Co., 1980). The authors compiled their data primarily from census, church, justice of the peace, land, pension, probate, town, and vital records, plus account books of storekeepers, and court records that contain clear references to the race of plaintiffs and/or defendants.
136Cornelia Hughes Dayton, Women Before the Bar: Gender, Law, and Society in Connecticut, 1639-1789 (Chapel Hill: University of North Carolina Press, 1995).
137Coverture was the condition of being a married woman and under 18th century law, "a woman under coverture was allowed to sue only through personality of her husband." Black's Law Dictionary, 373.
138NLCC Files, Nov. 1741, Box 69, folder 14, no. 375.
139Ibid, June 1717, Box 12, folder 6.
140Ibid, June 1748, Box 85, folder 19.
141Ibid, June 1725, Box 22, folder 11, no. 165.
142Ibid, Feb. 1725, Box 21, folder 15, no. 47
143Ibid, Feb. 1804, Box 263, folder 1, no. 48.
144Ibid, Nov. 1849, Box 419, folder 17, no. 462
145Ibid, Feb. 1759,Box 110, folder 13, no. 22.
146Ibid, June 1772, Box 161, folder 5.
147Ibid, June 1772, Box 161, folder 16, no. 268.
148Bozrah v. Groton, Ibid, Mar. 1819, Box 327, folder 12; Lisbon v. Groton, Box 328, folder 3; Daniel Penhollow v. New London, Box 328, folder 6; Daniel Robbins v. John V. Robbins, Box 328, folder 7; Nathan Rose v. Griswold, Box 328, folder 7.
149Those wishing to make an institutional study of the court and its functions and the County Treasurer, Clerk, or jail will find the Trials volumes particularly relevant.
150Charles J. Hoadly ed., The Public Records of the Colony of Connecticut, Vol. 5 (Hartford: Case, Lockwood and Brainard, 1870), 48.
151Biographies of two leading Connecticut lawyers, Jared Ingersoll and William Samuel Johnson, have been written. The authors assert that they were the two leading lawyers in the colony, but in neither case is this argument backed by a close examination of county or superior court records. Lawrence Henry Gipson, Jared Ingersoll: A Study of American Loyalism in Relation to the British Colonial Government (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1920, reprinted 1970); Elizabeth P. McCaughey, From Loyalist to Founding Father: The Political Odyssey of William Samuel Johnson (New York: Columbia University Press, 1980.
Arrangement
The county court usually met three times per year, in February, June, and November and the records for each session are arranged in numerical order beginning in 1716.152 Files are arranged generally in numerical and alphabetical order by surname of plaintiff beginning in February 1739. The records for the June and November sessions followed a standard pattern. Continuances and reviews were the first cases heard and decided and are generally in the worst physical condition. Reviews represent cases that had been decided at one court, but the losing party asked for a review of the verdict at a subsequent court. Continued cases are those in which no decision has been rendered at one court session and action is deferred to a later one. New cases follow and comprise the bulk of the cases decided in each session, while cases prosecuted by the King's or State's Attorney are found at the end of records for the session or at the appropriate alphabetical location. Until June 1744, non-adjudicated cases were interfiled with cases for which decisions were made. Beginning at that term of the county court, however, no docket cases come last and are filed in alphabetical order. The pattern for February sessions is slightly different. Adjourned cases are heard first, followed by numerical cases, and beginning in June 1744 followed by no docket cases. A court session may, therefore, have three or four alphabetical arrangements of documents, for reviews, continuances, new cases, and no docket cases.
The arrangement changed in 1769 with the disappearance of record books for Trials. Files are then arranged in a single alphabetical sequence, mixing continuances, new cases, and non-adjudicated cases. In November 1781, however, with the appearance of Vol. 26 of Trials, the pre-1769 numerical pattern re-emerges. No Docket cases cease with the June 18ll court, except for the December 1816 and November 1822 sessions. For the period between June 1817 and June 1835, all cases are filed in alphabetical order, but the ordering reverts to numbers in December 1835 with the beginning of separate Docket volumes.
November 1781, however, with the appearance of Vol. 26 of Trials, the pre-1769 numerical pattern re-emerges. No Docket cases cease with the June 18ll court, except for the December 1816 and November 1822 sessions. For the period between June 1817 and June 1835, all cases are filed in alphabetical order, but the ordering reverts to numbers in December 1835 with the beginning of separate Docket volumes.
Endnotes
152For several years after the American Revolution and into the 19th century, the pattern was not always consistent, as the February court session sometimes convened in March and the November session in December.
Related Material
The volumes for Trials contain more information, particularly for the period up to about 1720 and Papers by Subject include useful supplementary information in several series, particularly Costs, Executions, and Summons for Evidence.
In addition to Dockets, Trials, and Papers by Subject already discussed, the most closely related records are those of the New London County Superior Court. The bulk of cases heard by the Superior Court consisted of appeals from the lower court.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. County Court (New London County)
Subjects:
County courts -- Connecticut -- New London County -- History; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut. County Court (New London County) -- History; Connecticut. Judicial Dept. -- History
Document Types:
Civil court records; Criminal Court records; Judicial records
Restrictions on Access
Many of the papers found in Files> for the New London County Court are fragile and they must be handled with great care. Photocopies have been inserted in place of originals for materials on African Americans, Native Americans, and for other items considered to be particularly valuable.
See the policy.
Provenance
The county clerks were responsible for gathering, organizing, and preserving the records for the New London County Court. They were transferred to the Connecticut State Library in 1921.
Container List
- Files, 1691-1855
  - 1691-1692 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1693 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - 1696 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1698 (Box 1, Folder 5-8)
  - 1699 (Box 1, Folder 9-12)
  - 1700 (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
  - 1701 (Box 1, Folder 17-21)
  - 1702 (Box 1)
    - February (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - June (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
    - June (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - September (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1703 (Box 2)
    - March (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - June (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
    - September (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - 1704 (Box 2)
    - June (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - September (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
    - November (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
  - 1705 (Box 2)
    - June (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
    - June (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - September (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
    - November (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1706 (Box 3)
    - June (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
    - September (Box 3, Folder 11-14)
  - 1707 (Box 3)
    - June (Box 3, Folder 15-19)
    - September (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - 1708 (Box 4)
    - June (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
    - September (Box 4, Folder 7-11)
  - 1709 (Box 4)
    - April (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - June (Box 4, Folder 13-17)
    - September (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - 1710 (Box 4)
    - June (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
    - September (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
  - 1711 (Box 5)
    - June (Box 5, Folder 9-14)
    - September (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - November (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
    - November (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - 1712 (Box 6)
    - June (Box 6, Folder 3-7)
    - August (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - November (Box 6, Folder 9-13)
  - 1713 (Box 6)
    - June (Box 6, Folder 14-18)
    - November (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - November (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
  - 1714 (Box 7)
    - June (Box 7, Folder 8-16)
    - November (Box 7, Folder 17-19)
    - November (Box 8, Folder 1-6)
  - 1715 (Box 8)
    - February (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - June (Box 8, Folder 10-16)
    - August (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
    - August (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - November (Box 9, Folder 4-15)
  - 1716 (Box 9)
    - February (Box 9, Folder 16-19)
    - February (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - June (Box 10, Folder 2-5)
    - August (Box 10, Folder 6-11)
    - November (Box 10, Folder 12-20)
    - November (Box 11, Folder 1-10)
  - 1717 (Box 11)
    - February (Box 11, Folder 11-16)
    - June, no. 1-28 (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
    - June, no. 29-76, miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
    - August (Box 12, Folder 8-12)
    - November (Box 12, Folder 13-18)
  - 1718 (Box 12)
    - March, no. 1-26 (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
    - March, no. 27-53, miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 1-7)
    - June (Box 13, Folder 8-15)
    - November, no. 1-72 (Box 13, Folder 16-21)
    - November, no. 76-139, special and no dockets (Box 14, Folder 1-6)
  - 1719 (Box 14)
    - June (Box 14, Folder 7-18)
    - November, no. 1-15 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
    - November, no. 16-115, miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 1-12)
  - 1720 (Box 15)
    - February (Box 15, Folder 13-18)
    - June, no. 1-8 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - June, no. 11-101, miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 1-7)
    - November (Box 16, Folder 8-20)
  - 1721 (Box 17)
    - February (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
    - June (Box 17, Folder 6-13)
    - November (Box 17, Folder 15-20)
  - 1722 (Box 18)
    - February, no. 2-45 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - June (Box 18, Folder 4-11)
    - November (Box 18, Folder 12-19)
  - 1723 (Box 18)
    - February, no. 1-15 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - February, no. 16-74 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
    - June (Box 19, Folder 5-14)
    - November, no. 1-101 (Box 19, Folder 16-21)
    - November, no. 102-119 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - 1724 (Box 20)
    - February (Box 20, Folder 3-8)
    - June, no. 1-130 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
    - June, no.131-143 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - August (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - November (Box 21, Folder 3-12)
  - 1725 (Box 21)
    - February (Box 21, Folder 13-19)
    - June (Box 22, Folder 1-12)
    - November, no. 1-145 (Box 22, Folder 13-20)
    - November, no. 146-198 (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
  - 1726 (Box 23)
    - February (Box 23, Folder 5-14)
    - June, no. 1-108 (Box 23, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no. 109-252 (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
    - August (Box 24, Folder 10-14)
    - November, no. 2-105 (Box 24, Folder 15-20)
    - November, no. 106-162 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - 1727 (Box 25)
    - February (Box 25, Folder 5-11)
    - June, no. 1-163 (Box 25, Folder 12-21)
    - June, no. 165-245 (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
    - November (Box 26, Folder 7-18)
  - 1728 (Box 26)
    - February, no. 2-33 (Box 26, Folder 19-20)
    - February, no. 34-125 (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no. 1-240 (Box 27, Folder 6-19)
    - June, no. 242-270 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - November (Box 28, Folder 3-16)
  - 1729 (Box 28)
    - February, no. 1-80 (Box 28, Folder 17-20)
    - February, no. 82-165 (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no. 2-267 (Box 29, Folder 5-20)
    - June, no. 269-333 (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
    - November (Box 30, Folder 5-17)
  - 1730 (Box 30)
    - February, no. 2-55 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - February, no. 56-190 (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
    - June (Box 31, Folder 8-18)
    - November, no. 1-33 (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
    - November, no. 34-203 (Box 32, Folder 1-8)
  - 1731 (Box 32)
    - February (Box 32, Folder 9-14)
    - June, no 1-89 (Box 32, Folder 15-19)
    - June, no. 90-268 (Box 33, Folder 1-9)
    - November, no. 1-198 (Box 33, Folder 10-20)
    - November, no. 199-257 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
  - 1732 (Box 34)
    - February (Box 34, Folder 5-12)
    - June, no. 2-122 (Box 34, Folder 13-19)
    - June, no. 123-364 (Box 34, Folder 13-19)
    - November, no. 1-105 (Box 35, Folder 14-19)
    - November, no. 106-279 (Box 36, Folder 1-11)
  - 1733 (Box 36)
    - February, no. 2-155 (Box 36, Folder 12-19)
    - February, no. 156-184 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - June (Box 37, Folder 3-16)
    - November, no. 1-40 (Box 37, Folder 17-19)
    - November, no. 41-297 (Box 38, Folder 1-16)
  - 1734 (Box 38)
    - February, no. 1-68 (Box 38, Folder 17-20)
    - February, no. 69-218 (Box 39, Folder 1-9)
    - June, no. 2-151 (Box 39, Folder 10-19)
    - June, no. 152-320 (Box 40, Folder 1-11)
    - November, no. 1-141 (Box 40, Folder 12-20)
    - November, no. 142-364 (Box 41, Folder 1-15)
  - 1735 (Box 41)
    - January, no. 2-76 (Box 41, Folder 16-20)
    - January, no. 77-194 (Box 42, Folder 1-9)
    - June, no. 2-167 (Box 42, Folder 10-20)
    - June, no. 168-427 (Box 43, Folder 1-17)
    - November no. 1-31 (Box 43, Folder 18-21)
    - November, no. 32-318 (Box 44)
  - 1736 (Box 45)
    - January (Box 45, Folder 1-10)
    - June, no. 1-127 (Box 45, Folder 11-20)
    - June, no. 128-382 (Box 46, Folder 1-16)
    - July (Box 46, Folder 17-18)
    - August (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - November (Box 47, Folder 1-18)
  - 1737 (Box 47)
    - February, no. 1-27 (Box 47, Folder 19-20)
    - February, no. 28-233 (Box 48, Folder 1-14)
    - June, no. 1-91 (Box 48, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no. 93-417 (Box 49)
    - June, no. 418-542 (Box 50, Folder 1-8)
    - November, no. 1-175 (Box 50, Folder 9-20)
    - November, no. 176-439 (Box 51, Folder 1-17)
  - 1738 (Box 51)
    - February, no. 4-40 (Box 51, Folder 18-20)
    - February, no. 42-288 (Box 52, Folder 1-16)
    - June, no. 1-52 (Box 52, Folder 17-20)
    - June, no. 59-371 (Box 53)
    - June, no. 372-497 (Box 54, Folder 1-10)
    - November, no. 3-155 (Box 54, Folder 11-20)
    - November, no. 156-364 (Box 55, Folder 1-17)
  - 1739 (Box 55)
    - February, no. 1-41 (Box 55, Folder 18-20)
    - February, no. 42-332 (Box 56, Folder 1-19)
    - June, no. 1-283 (Box 57, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 284-519 (Box 58, Folder 1-16)
    - November, no. 2-66 (Box 58, Folder 17-20)
    - November, no. 69-384 (Box 59, Folder 1-20)
    - November, no. 385-438 (Box 60, Folder 1-4)
  - 1740 (Box 60)
    - February, no. 3-257 (Box 60, Folder 5-20)
    - February, no. 259-472 (Box 61, Folder 1-13)
    - June, no. 1-117 (Box 61, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no. 118-425 (Box 62, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 426-652 (Box 63, Folder 1-14)
    - November, no. 1-103 (Box 63, Folder 15-21)
    - November, no. 104-441 (Box 64, Folder 1-20)
    - November, no. 443-555 (Box 65, Folder 1-7)
  - 1741 (Box 65)
    - February, no. 1-254 (Box 65, Folder 8-20)
    - February, no. 255-431 (Box 66, Folder 1-10)
    - June, no. 1-150 (Box 66, Folder 11-20)
    - June, no. 151-507 (Box 67, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 509-695 (Box 68, Folder 1-13)
    - November, no. 1-145 (Box 68, Folder 14-21)
    - November, no. 146-503 (Box 69, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 504-616 (Box 70, Folder 1-7)
  - 1742 (Box 70)
    - February, no. 2-240 (Box 70, Folder 8-21)
    - February, no. 241-450 (Box 71, Folder 1-12)
    - June, no. 1-139 (Box 71, Folder 13-21)
    - June, no. 142-477 (Box 72, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 478-634 (Box 73, Folder 1-9)
    - November, no. 1-193 (Box 73, Folder 10-20)
    - November, no. 194-334 (Box 74, Folder 1-8)
  - 1743 (Box 74)
    - February, no. 2-228 (Box 74, Folder 9-20)
    - February, no. 229-240 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - June, no. 1-336 (Box 75, Folder 2-20)
    - November, no. 1-260 (Box 76, Folder 1-15)
  - 1744 (Box 76)
    - February, no. 1-93 (Box 76, Folder 16-21)
    - February, no. 94-207 (Box 77, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no. 4-194 (Box 77, Folder 8-20)
    - June, no. 195-205 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - June, no docket (Avery-Woodbridge) (Box 78, Folder 2-6)
    - November, no. 1-163 (Box 78, Folder 7-17)
    - November, no docket (Armstrong-Woodbridge) (Box 78, Folder 18-22)
  - 1745
    - February, no. 1-129 (Box 79, Folder 1-9)
    - February, no docket (Billings-Winthrop) (Box 79, Folder 10-13)
    - June, no. 1-116 (Box 79, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no. 117-179 (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Woodbridge) (Box 80, Folder 5-10)
    - November, no. 1-128 (Box 80, Folder 11-19)
    - November, no docket (Andrus-Curtiss) (Box 80, Folder 20)